Finding Aid for Center for Afroamerican and African Studies (University of Michigan) records, 1966-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio recordings on cassettes 1975-2001
  - Early Recorded Speakers
    - Joel Samoff: Ujamaa: Poverty and Socialism in Tanzania 1978-11-01, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-56-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-56-2
    - Joel Samoff: Crisis and Socialism in Tanzania 1980-04-04, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-57-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-57-2
    - Sarkisian: Sarkisian Lecture undated, audiocassette (Box 28)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-58-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-58-2
    - Monica Schuler: The African Religious Tradition in Jamaica 1979-11-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-59-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-59-2
    - Harold Shapiro: “UM: A Decade After BAM” and Panel: “The Organization and Significance of BAM” 1980-03-20, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-60-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-60-2
    - Smith, Varner, Hefner, Mann, Yates: Panel: “Perspectives on BAM from the University Community 1980-03-20, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-61-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-61-2
    - Geneva Smitherman: World of the Black Child 1975-06-25, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-62-1
    - Mabel Smythe: The Elusive Goal of African Economic Development 1984-03-14, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-63-1
    - Donald Spivey: Race-Building, Separatism, and Education in the US 1978-10-11, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-64-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-64-2
    - Robert Staples: Beyond the Black Family 1979-02-21, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-65-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-65-2
    - Cynthia Stevens: The Shrinking Economy, Racism, and Sexism 1984-03-28, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-66-1
    - Curtis Stokes: Fanon and Turosky: Problems with Revolutionary Universalism 1979-03-21, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-67-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-67-2
    - Pauline Stone: Feminist Consciousness and the Black Woman 1977-10-26, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-68-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-68-2
    - Niara Sudarkasa: On the Relationship Between African and Afro-American Family Structure 1981-01-21, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-69-1
    - Niara Sudarkasa: World of a Black Child: African Beginnings undated, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-70-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-70-2
    - Raymond Tanter: American Foreign Policy: The Middle Eastern and Southern Africa 1978-11-29, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-71-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-71-2
    - Mike Thelwell and Walter Rodney: Lecture 1984-04-02, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-72-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-72-2
    - Michael Thornton: Black People in the Far East: A Sociohistorical Perspective 1981-02-18, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-73-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-73-2
    - Ronald Waters: Black Americans and the Domestic Political Agenda in the 1980s 1980-01-30, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-74-1
    - Wheeler, Foster, Moody, Stone: UM a Decade After BAM 1980-03-20, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-75-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-75-2
    - Clarisse Zimra and Robert O'Meally: Black Critical Theory 1985-04-24, audiocassette
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-76-1
  - Jamaica Study Abroad
    - Charles Val Carnegie: Caribbean Preconceived 1991-05-27, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-77-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-77-2
    - Charles Val Carnegie: Carnegie: Caribbean Preconceived (side a); Various: Dub Poetry Reading (side b) 1991-05-27, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-78-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-78-2
    - Lucille Mair: Jamaica in a Regional and World Context 1991-05-28, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-79-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-79-2
    - Lucille Mair: Jamaica in a Regional and World Context 1991-05-28, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-80-1
    - Kamau Brathwaite: History and Poetics 1991-05-30, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-81-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-81-2
    - Kamau Brathwaite & Wilma Bailey: History and Poetics (side a); 1991-06-03 – Dr. Wilma Bailey (side b) 1991-05-30, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-82-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-82-2
    - Garth White: Reggae and Rastafari 1991-05-30, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-83-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-83-2
    - Garth White and Charles Val Carnegie: White: Reggae and Rastafari (side a); Carnegie: Jamaican People and the Emergence of Identity (side b) 1991-05-30, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-84-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-84-2
    - Charles Val Carnegie: Jamaican People and the Emergence of Identity 1991-06-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-85-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-85-2
    - Kathryn Shields-Brodber: Jamaican Language 1991-06-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-86-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-86-2
    - Kathryn Shields-Brodber & Swithin Wilmot: Shields-Brodber: Jamaican Language (side a); Wilmot: Black Political Experience Since Freedom (side b) 1991-06-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-87-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-87-2
    - Swithin Wilmot: Black Political Experience Since Freedom 1991-06-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-88-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-88-2
    - Muriel Carnegie: An Evening with Muriel Carnegie 1991-06-04, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-89-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-89-2
    - Wilmot Perkins: Visiting KLAS Radio with Wilmot Perkins 1991-06-10, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-90-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-90-2
    - Walter Allen: Comparative Study of the Black Male in female-Headed Households in the United States and the Caribbean 1991-06-11, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-91-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-91-2
    - Franklin McKnight: Newspaper Publishing in an Oral Society 1991-06-12, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-92-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-92-2
    - Franklin McKnight: Newspaper Publishing in an Oral Society 1991-06-12, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-93-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-93-2
    - Carolyn Cooper: Dynamics of Cultural Production 1991-06-14, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-94-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-94-2
    - Carolyn Cooper and Trevor Monroe: Cooper: Dynamics of Cultural Production (side a); 1991-06-17 - Monroe: Jamaican Political Economy; The Present Conjecture (side b) 1991-06-14, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-95-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-95-2
    - Trevor Monroe: Jamaican Political Economy: The Present Conjecture 1991-06-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-96-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-96-2
    - Arnold Bertram and Joan Gordon-Wembley: Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics 1991-06-18, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-97-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-97-2
    - Arnold Bertram, Joan Gordon-Wembley and Rupert Lewis: Bertram & Gordon-Wembley: Disaffected Perspectives on Jamaican Politics” (side a); 1991-06-19 Lewis: Garvey Movement (side b) 1991-06-18, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-98-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-98-2
    - Rupert Lewis: Garvey Movement 1991-06-19, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-99-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-99-2
    - Thomas Holt: The Problem of Freedom 1991-06-19, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-100-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-100-2
    - Velma Pollard: Reading Velma Pollard 1991-06-20, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-101-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-101-2
    - Irena Cousins, Donovan Crawford, Neville James and Paul Thomas: Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment 1991-06-21, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-102-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-102-2
    - Irena Cousins, Donovan Crawford, Neville James, Paul Thomas and Elsa Leo-Rhynie: Cousins, et al: Panel Discussion on the Jamaican Business Environment (side a); 1991-06-24 - Leo-Rhynie: Status of Women in Jamaica (side b) 1991-06-21, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-103-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-103-2
    - Elsa Leo-Rhynie: Status of Women in Jamaica 1991-06-24, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-104-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-104-2
    - Baston Lee: A Visit with Baston Lee 1991-06-27, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-105-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-105-2
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #1 1991-05-13, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-106-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-106-2
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #2 1991-05-14, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-107-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-107-2
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #3 1991-05-15, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-108-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-108-2
    - Study Abroad in Jamaica Orientation #4 1991-05-16, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-109-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-109-2
  - Gender and Urban Poverty Conference
    - Panel 1 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-110-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-110-2
    - Panel 2 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-111-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-111-2
    - Panel 2 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-112-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-112-2
    - Panel 3 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-113-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-113-2
    - Panel 3 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-114-1
    - Panel 4 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-115-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-115-2
    - Panel 4 1996-05-17, audiocassette (Box 29)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-116-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-116-2
  - Brown Bag
    - Nesha Z. Haniff: Successful Caribbean Women: We had the courage and the vision 1986-12-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-117-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-117-2
    - Adelbert Jenkins: Sustaining self-esteem 1987-03-26, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-118-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-118-2
    - Nesha Haniff: Blaze of Fire: The significant contributions of Caribbean women (A redefinition of success) 1989-02-15, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-119-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-119-2
    - Carlene J. Edie: The Seaga to Manley: The impact of the dependency crisis on the 1989 Jamaican Elections 1989-03-29, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-120-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-120-2
    - James Jackson: Cross-national perspectives on racism 1990-10-02, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-121-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-121-2
    - Ruth Massinga: Community action for urban and minority students in 1990 1990-10-30, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-122-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-122-2
    - Harold Cruse: Plural but equal: A critical study of blacks and minorities in America's plural society: Implications for ethnic pluralism in the United States 1990-11-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-123-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-123-2
    - Michael Dawson: Models of black voting behavior 1990-11-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-124-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-124-2
    - Keletso Atkins: Questionable haven: 19th century emigration schemes for black American settlement in South Africa 1990-11-13, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-125-1
    - Peter Kareithi: The erosion of democracy in Kenya 1990-11-16, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-126-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-126-2
    - Barry Kistnasamy: Health in transition: Towards a post-apartheid South Africa 1990-11-20, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-127-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-127-2
    - Maria Grosz-Ngate: Reflections on class formation in contemporary Mali 1990-11-27, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-128-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-128-2
    - Nesha Haniff: Trying to define indigenous feminist movement among women of color 1990-12-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-129-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-129-2
    - Neil Foley: The New South in the Southwest: Anglos, Blacks and Chicanos in Central Texas 1880-1930 1990-12-11, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-130-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-130-2
    - Donald R. Deskins, Jr.: Prospects for minority doctorates in the year 2000: Employment opportunities in a changing America 1991-01-15, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-131-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-131-2
    - Oscar A. Barbarin: Health and poverty in African-American families: Coping with Sickle Cell Disease 1991-01-22, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-132-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-132-2
    - Robert Chrisman: Richard Wright: How Black Women are Portrayed in his Works 1991-01-29, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-133-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-133-2
    - Donna Cochran and Carol Cummings: Cross-Cultural Analyses Women’s Health and Well Being: Research at the Institute of Jamaica 1991-02-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-134-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-134-2
    - William McGinley: Literacy as Voice: Understanding Children’s Writing About Their Communities and Their Lives 1991-02-12, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-135-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-135-2
    - Ada Ferrer: Race and Nationalism in Eastern Cuba 1991-02-19, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-136-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-136-2
    - Huma Ibrahim: Bessie Head: ‘Third World’ Writer in Exile 1991-03-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-137-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-137-2
    - Teshome G. Wagaw: The Continued Dilemma of Ethnocentrism in Education: African-American Dimensions 1991-03-12, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-138-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-138-2
    - David Labiosa: Strategies of Resistance and Affirmation in 20th Century Caribbean Narrative 1991-03-19, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-139-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-139-2
    - Todd Shaw: The Making of Black Mayors: The Black Voter’s Criteria for Supporting Black Mayoral Candidacies 1991-03-26, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-140-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-140-2
    - Andrew Williams: The Evolution of Ethnicity Among the African Americans of the Dominican Republic 1991-04-02, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-141-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-141-2
    - N. Frank Ukadike: Colonialism, Christian Missionaries, and African Cinema 1991-04-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-142-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-142-2
    - Robert Chrisman, Murray Jackson and Melba Boyd: Poetry reading 1991-06-11, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-143-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-143-2
    - Melba Boyd and Lemuel Johnson: Poetry reading 1991-06-25, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-144-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-144-2
    - Myron Hardy: Poetry Reading 1991-07-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-145-1
    - Elise Bryant: Poetry reading 1991-07-16, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-146-1
    - Teshome G. Wagaw: The Horn of Africa in Turmoil: The Challenge of Confederation 1991-09-17, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-147-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-147-2
    - Earl Lewis: Reflections on South Africa 1991-09-24, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-148-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-148-2
    - Sharon P. Holland: Approaches to the Cross-Cultural Study of Native American and African-American Fiction 1991-10-01, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-149-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-149-2
    - Daria C. Kirby: Affirmative Action Programs: An Institutional Analysis 1991-10-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-150-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-150-2
    - Christopher McAuley: The Trinidadian World System: The Work of Cox, James, and Padmore 1991-10-15, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-151-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-151-2
    - Andrea G. Hunter: Constructing Gender: An Exploration of Afro-American Men’s Conceptualization of Manhood 1991-10-22, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-152-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-152-2
    - Director: The CAAS Study Abroad in Jamaica Program: For Prospective Students, A Discussion with the Director and Former Participants in the Spring Term Program in Kingston 1991-10-29, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-153-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-153-2
    - Tracye Matthews: Women in the Black Panther Party 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-154-1
    - Lisa Lindsay: Brazilians in Lagos: A Social History 1991-11-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-155-1
    - Neal Sobania: Contemporaneous Parts Among East African Pastoralists 1991-11-12, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-156-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-156-2
    - Ronald E. Mickens: First Black Physicists: Bouchet and Imes: An Historical Perspective of African-American Scientists 1991-11-18, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-157-1
    - Afaf Omer: Ethnicity and the Sexual Division of Labor in Sudanese Agriculture 1991-12-03, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-158-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-158-2
    - Nancy Mirabal: Extending the Taboo: Afro-Cubans in Ybor City, 1890-1920 1992-01-28, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-159-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-159-2
    - Francille Rusan Wilson: Carter G. Woodson and ‘The Mis-Education of the Negro’ 1992-02-11, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-160-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-160-2
    - Sheldon H. Danziger: Poverty and Inequality in the 1980’s 1992-02-18, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-161-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-161-2
    - Charles Hammerslough: Demographic Transition in Kenya: Causes and Prospects 1992-03-03, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-162-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-162-2
    - Cecilia Green: At the Junction of the Global and the Local: Transnational Industry and Women’s Workers in the Caribbean 1992-03-10, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-163-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-163-2
    - Uzo Esonwanne: Enlightenment Epistemology and ‘Aesthetic Cognition’: Mariama Ba’s ‘So Long a Letter’ 1992-03-17, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-164-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-164-2
    - Elsa Barkley Brown: Many Ways of Being Political 1992-03-31, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-165-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-165-2
    - Verene Sheperd: Immigrant Laborers in Jamaica after the Abolition of Slavery 1992-04-14, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-166-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-166-2
    - Kyra Gaunt: Hip-hop music: 'Breaking' with tradition 1992-09-22, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-167-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-167-2
    - Cathy J. Cohen: Power, resistance, and marginalization: Two communities respond to the AIDS epidemic 1992-10-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-168-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-168-2
    - Rebecca J. Scott: Building, bridging and breaching the color line: Collective action in Louisiana and Cuba after Emancipation 1992-10-20, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-169-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-169-2
    - Yvonne "Baubie" Paschal: Community-based literacy programs 1992-10-13, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-170-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-170-2
    - Teshome G. Wagaw, Afaf Omer and Paula Tavrow: Conflict in the Horn of Africa: Background to the Crisis in Somalia 1993-01-19, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-171-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-171-2
    - Claude Clegg: A Splendid type of colored American: Charles Young and the re-organization of the Liberian Frontier force under African-American leadership, 1912-1913 1993-02-02, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-173-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-173-2
    - Susan Jenkins: The meaning of skin color among young African-American Women 1993-02-04, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-174-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-174-2
    - Guthrie P. Ramsey, Jr.: Africa, cultural dialogics, and the foundation of modern jazz 1993-02-16, audiocassette (Box 30)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-175-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-175-2
    - Gracia C. Clark: African feminism and "Development" 1993-03-02, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-176-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-176-2
    - Anthea Morrison: Elusive Ancestors: The quest for origins in Les derniers rois mages by Maryse Conde 1993-03-16, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-178-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-178-2
    - John Matlock: A discussion of two African-Americans' traditional wedding in West Africa and their friendship with African students 1993-03-23, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-179-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-179-2
    - Robert A. Brown, III: A tale of two cities: The dilemma of African-American urban representation 1993-03-30, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-180-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-180-2
    - Veronica Gregg: The invention of Caribbean women undated, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-182-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-182-2
    - Charles D. Moody, Sr.: The University of Michigan South Africa Initiative 1993-09-28, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-183-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-183-2
    - Ahmad Abdur Rahman: Racism in the criminal justice system 1993-10-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-184-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-184-2
    - Andrew L. Williams: Haitian legacies: African-American settlement and culture in the Dominican Republic, 1824-1940 1993-10-17, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-185-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-185-2
    - Moffat Mogane: Grassroots organizing in South Africa: Challenges and opportunities 1993-10-26, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-186-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-186-2
    - Dorceta Taylor: Women of color, environmental justice and ecofeminism 1993-11-02, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-187-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-187-2
    - Elizabeth James: Libraries and literacy: The missing link for children's acquisition of learning skills 1993-11-04, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-188-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-188-2
    - Nancy Hopkins: The social and political impact of the African-American Scientist: Futuristic scenarios 1993-11-30, audiocassette (Box 31)
      - [side 1], 2012140-SR-190-1
      - [side 2], 2012140-SR-190-2